Guide to the Anne Morrow Lindbergh Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence from friends and acquaintances, 1915-1973; Series I
  Arrangement
  The series is arranged alphabetically. Letters of a particular correspondent are arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  The series consists of letters Lindbergh received from a large circle of friends and acquaintances. For Lindbergh's replies to the letters in this series, see the appropriate dates in Series VI, Outgoing correspondence.
  By contemporary standards the correspondence is prolific and reveals the important role that friendship played in her life. Some of the people who corresponded with her from childhood on include Lucia (Norton) Valentine, Amy Aldrich, Vernon Munroe, Jr., Sue (Vaillant) Hatt, and Corliss Lamont. The correspondence of another childhood friend, Elizabeth "Dizzy' Hart, is of interest for the picture it gives of Anne Morrow Lindbergh as a school girl.
  Major correspondents whose relationships with Lindbergh were particularly close and whose correspondence is voluminous include Dana Atchley, Ernestine (Stodelle) Chamberlain, Corliss Lamont, and Ruth (Thomas) Oliff. Other important correspondents include Dom Alexis (Abbot of Boquen), Anne Carrel (wife of Alexis Carrel), Harry Guggenheim, Harold and Nigel Nicolson,Vita Sackville-West, Igor Sikorsky, Truman and Katherine Smith, Eleanor and James Newton, Kitty Taquey, John Oldrin, and Helen and Kurt Wolff.
  After college, Lindbergh remained in contact with two Smith College faculty members, Mina (Kirstein) Curtiss and Marthe Sturm. The correspondence from Curtiss is especially interesting because of the close friendship that developed between the former English professor and the writer.
  Lindbergh corresponded with a number of artists, writers, and journalists. There is correspondence from Betsey Barton, Evelyn Ames, Jean Stafford, Sylvia Shaw Judson, Selden Rodman, Isabel La Follette, Russell Leffingwell, Lauren Dwight (Deac) Lyman, Carl Milles, Florida Scott-Maxwell, Mary Ellen Chase, and Stanley R. Ross.
  America First activities are documented in correspondence from Kathleen Norris, Katrina Romney, Thelma Lee, and Sue (Vaillant) Hatt. Former employees (secretaries and children's nurses) with whom Lindbergh continued to correspond include Betty Gow, Felice Hankey, Gertrude Gloor, Judy Frautschi, Monte Millar, Marta (Brodie) Norris, Barbara Mansfield, Christine (Gawne) Wick, and Jean Saunders.
  - Adams, J. Donald, 1939-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams, Jane
    General
    See: Greene, Jane (Adams), box 7, folder 147
  - Aldrich, Amey Own, 1920-1963, undated (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
  - Alexis, Dom, 1938-1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen, Helen, 1953-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Almy, Dorothy, 1943-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ament, Mishi, 1950-1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ames, Evelyn, 1940-1973, undated (Box 1, Folder 9-19)
  - Armstrong, Christa, 1955-1973 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Armstrong, Hamilton Fish, 1955-1968 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Astor, Michael, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Astor, Nancy, 1936-1955 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Atchley, Dana, 1947-1959 (Box 2, Folder 23-34)
  - Atchley, Dana, 1960-1973 (Box 3, Folder 35-41)
  - Atchley, Mary, 1949-1973 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Bacon, Elizabeth
    See: Rodenwald, Elizabeth (Bacon), boxes 19-20, folders 379-382
  - Baker, Rachel, 1955-1968 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Barber, Elsie
    See: Trask, Elsie (Barber), box 22, folders 435-437
  - Barry, Alice, 1956-1967 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Bartlett, Margaret, 1958-1968
    See: Millar, Margaret (Bartlett) "Monte", boxes 13-14, folders 263-288
  - Bartlett, Toto (Foster), 1958-1968 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Barton, Betsey, 1944-1962, undated (Box 3, Folder 46-47)
  - Bassage, Anne, 1947-1962 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Bechtel, Nancy, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Beck, Susanna, 1970
    See: Hatt, Sue (Vaillant), boxes 8-9, folders 163-179
  - Benton, William, 1945-1973 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Benton, Helen, 1945-1973 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Bigelow, Poultney, 1938-1947 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Bingham, Alfred M., 1926-1943 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Bixby, Elizabeth "Debby", 1930-1968 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Bixby, Harold M., 1930, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Bliss, Zaidee
    See:Goodyear, Zaidee (Bliss), box 7, folder 142
  - Boël, Thilda, 1939-1944, undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Brandt, Laura
    See: Stevens, Laura (Brandt), box 21, folders 419-420
  - Breckinridge, Aida, 1930-1942 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Breckinridge, Henry, 1934-1939 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    See also: Publisher's correspondence, Series III. Other publishers, boxes 73-74, folders 41-61
  - Brett, Midge G., 1923-1925, undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Brewster, Kingman, Jr., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Brodie, Marta
    See: Norris, Marta (Brodie), box 16, folder 322
  - Bromley, Kate Thompson, 1928-1959 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Bryher, Winifred, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Burchell, Cornelia W., 1922-1924 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Burnett, Charles, 1928-1942, undated (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Burnett, Susan, 1929-1960, undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Byard, Maggie, 1947-1963 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Byard, Paul, 1959-1963 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Carey, Patricia
    See: Troy, Patricia (Carey), box 22, folder 438
  - Carrel, Anne, 1936-1949 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Ceresole, Lise, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Chamberlain, Ernestine (Stodelle), 1950-1958 (Box 4, Folder 69-76)
  - Chamberlain, Ernestine (Stodelle), 1959-1973, undated (Box 5, Folder 77-85)
  - Chase, Mary Ellen, 1928-1962 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Chilton, Constance, 1936-1948 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Chubbuck, Alys Jeanne, 1944-1948 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Churchill, Mary (Hand), 1936-1940, undated (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Crepin, Jean M., 1948-1959 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Curtiss, Mina (Kirstein), 1928-1972, undated (Box 5, Folder 90-96)
  - Dam, Andreas, 1933-1936 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Damon, Jean (Shields), 1947-1959 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Damon, Jean (Shields), 1960-1969, undated (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Davie, Emily, 1952-1958, undated (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Davis, Wellesley Parson, 1921-1967, undated (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Decoux, Janet, 1943-1971, undated (Box 6, Folder 102-106)
  - Dekino, Barbara (Mansfield)
    See: Mansfield, Barbara, box 12, folders 258
  - Delafield, Mary (Walker), 1920-1942, 1955-1973 (Box 6, Folder 107-109)
  - Delattre, André, 1944-1952 (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Delattre, Yvonne, 1944-1973, undated (Box 6, Folder 111-116)
  - De Pomereu, Robert, 1951-1961, undated (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - De Selincourt, Nancy
    See: Hunter-Gray, Nancy (de Selincourt), box 9, folder 188
  - Detroyat, Fanny, 1938-1948, undated (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Doubleday, Frank, 1915-1930, undated (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - DeWolf, Mary, 1944-1947 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Dreier, Barbara (Loines), 1940-1957, undated (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Dreier, Theodore, 1940-1969 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Dulles, Clover, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Dulles, Janet, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Dulles, John Foster, 1940-1955 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Earhart, Amelia, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Edmundson, D'arcy, 1947-1966, undated (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Fay, Laura "Bitta", 1926-1928, undated (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Ficke, Arthur Davison, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Flavin, Martin, 1944-1958, undated (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Forde, Eleanor
    See: Newton, Eleanor (Forde), box 15, folders 308-312
  - Foster, Toto
    See: Bartlett, Toto (Foster), box 3, folder 45
  - Franklin, Helena, 1958-1968 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Frautschi, Judith (Guild), 1952-1965, undated (Box 7, Folder 130-132)
  - Frederica, Queen of Greece, 1958, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Gaillard, Mary, 1922-1924, undated (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Gilder, Comfort, 1960-1972 (Box 7, Folder 135-136)
  - Gloor, Gertrude, 1947-1951 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Gonthiez, Jean, 1948-1955 (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Goodkind, Ruth, 1948-1950 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Goodwin, Lucy, 1921-1926 (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Goodyear, Conger, 1939-1962 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Goodyear, Zaidee (Bliss), 1928-1959, undated (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Gow, Betty, 1932-1936 (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Graeme, Jo, 1920-1939, undated (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Grant, Mary, 1952-1971, undated (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Gray, Marian, 1923-1925, undated (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Greene, Jane (Adams), 1936-1970, undated (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Greenslet, Ferris
    See: Publisher's correspondence, Series III. Other publishers, boxes 73-74, folders 41-61
  - Grenfell, Florrie
    See: St. Just, Florrie (Grenfell), box 20, folder 394
  - Gruenther, Alfred M., 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - Guggenheim, Harry F., 1934-1965 (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Guild, Judith
    See: Frautschi, Judith (Guild), box 7, folders 130-132
  - Hand, Francis, 1929-1939 (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - Hand, Francis, 1940-1962, undated (Box 8, Folder 151-152)
  - Hankey, Felice, 1944-1956, undated (Box 8, Folder 153-155)
  - Harcourt, Alfred
    See: Publisher's correspondence, Series III. Harcourt, Brace, and Company, box 72, folders 7-19
  - Harris, Louisa, 1938-1973, undated (Box 8, Folder 156-158)
  - Harris, Marguerite Tjader, 1951-1971 (Box 8, Folder 159)
  - Hart, Elizabeth "Dizzy", 1921-1930, undated (Box 8, Folder 160-162)
  - Hatt, Sue (Vaillant), 1929-1942 (Box 8, Folder 163-169)
  - Hatt, Sue (Vaillant), 1943-1973, undated (Box 9, Folder 170-179)
  - Hawks, E. M., 1935-1946 (Box 9, Folder 180)
  - Hayward, Leland, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 180)
  - Hocking, Ernest, 1952-1964 (Box 9, Folder 181)
  - Hooker, Helen, 1923-1926, undated (Box 9, Folder 182)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1940-1944 (Box 9, Folder 183)
    See also: Institutions, committees, and clubs, Series IX. Food for the Five Small Democracies, box 197, folders 40-44
  - Huber, Jack, 1948-1973, undated (Box 9, Folder 184-186)
  - Hulst, Maud, 1920-1948, undated (Box 9, Folder 187)
  - Hunter-Gray, Nancy (de Selincourt), 1937-1970 (Box 9, Folder 188)
  - Hutchison, Dorothy, 1940-1941
    See: Neild, Dorothy (Hutchison), box 15, folder 303
  - Ingalls, Laura, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 189)
  - Jackman, Libby (Sterling), 1961-1966 (Box 9, Folder 190)
  - Jay, Anne, 1960-1972, undated (Box 10, Folder 191)
  - Jennings, Ananda, 1960-1972, undated (Box 10, Folder 192)
  - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1963-1973 (Box 10, Folder 193)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 194)
  - Jones, Eleanor Robertson, 1920-1934, undated (Box 10, Folder 195-196)
  - Jovanovich, William
    See: Publisher's correspondence, Series III. Harcourt, Brace and World, boxes 72-73, folders 20-26
    See: Publisher's correspondence, Series III. Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, box 73, folder 27-30
  - Judson, Sylvia Shaw, 1942-1970, undated (Box 10, Folder 197-198)
  - Junken, Elizabeth, 1964-1971 (Box 10, Folder 199)
  - Kane, Amanda, 1937-1955, undated (Box 10, Folder 200)
  - Kennedy, Jacqueline, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 201)
  - Kennedy, Joseph P., 1938 (Box 10, Folder 202)
  - Kimball, Joy, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 203)
  - King, Stanley, 1933-1939 (Box 10, Folder 204)
  - Kirstein, Mina
    See: Curtiss, Mina (Kirstein), box 5, folder 90-96
  - Kline, Svea, 1944-1950 (Box 10, Folder 205)
  - Knecht, Martha, 1958-1965, undated (Box 10, Folder 206)
  - Knobel, Elsie, 1950-1964, undated (Box 10, Folder 207)
  - Knollenberg, Mary T., 1941-1956 (Box 10, Folder 208-209)
  - Kozol, Jonathan, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 210)
  - La Follette, Isabel, 1941-1973 (Box 10, Folder 211)
  - Lamb, Beatrice, 1944-1949 (Box 10, Folder 212)
  - Lamont, Austin, 1922-1969, undated (Box 10, Folder 213)
  - Lamont, Corliss, 1923-1948 (Box 10, Folder 214-216)
  - Lamont, Corliss, 1949-1973, undated (Box 11, Folder 217-227)
  - Lamont, Florence, 1936-1948 (Box 11, Folder 228)
  - Lamont, Helen (Lamb), 1963-1969 (Box 11, Folder 228)
  - Lamont, Margaret I., 1930-1946 (Box 11, Folder 228)
  - Lamont, Thomas Stilwell, 1939-1962 (Box 11, Folder 229)
  - Lamont, Thomas W., 1938 (Box 11, Folder 229)
  - Lang, Nancy, 1947-1953 (Box 11, Folder 230)
  - Lanier, Jean (Webster)
    See: Webster, Jean, box 24, folders 464-467
  - Leary, Marion, 1922-1928, undated (Box 11, Folder 231)
  - Lee, Jeanette, 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 232)
  - Lee, Thelma, 1934-1955, undated (Box 11, Folder 233-235)
  - Leffingwell, Russell, 1939-1960 (Box 11, Folder 236)
  - Lescaze, Mary, 1953-1969 (Box 12, Folder 237)
  - Lewis, C. S., 1947 (Box 12, Folder 238)
  - Lewis, Dorothy, 1962-1972, undated (Box 12, Folder 239)
  - Lockett, Japsy
    See: Sears, Japsy (Lockett), box 20, folder 403
  - Long, Haniel, 1939, 1950-1956 (Box 12, Folder 240)
  - Loomis, Sarah Dana, 1934-1938 (Box 12, Folder 241)
  - Love, Phillip, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 241)
  - Lowe, Victoria Lincoln, 1966-1969 (Box 12, Folder 242)
  - Lowell, Jean (Stafford)
    See: Stafford, Jean, box 21, folder 418
  - Lowell, Robert, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 243)
  - Luce, Clare Booth, Circa 1946, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 244)
  - Luen, Lao, 1921-1926, undated (Box 12, Folder 245)
  - Lyden, Ruth (Stephens), 1939-1972 (Box 12, Folder 246)
  - Lyman, Lauren Dwight "Deac", 1948-1970 (Box 12, Folder 247)
  - McBaron, Ruth, 1926-1933, undated (Box 12, Folder 248)
  - McCandless, Ruth, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 249)
  - McCormick, Katrina, 1941-1943 (Box 12, Folder 250-252)
  - McGavin, Ann, 1964-1969 (Box 12, Folder 253)
  - MacGregor, Robert, 1953-1967 (Box 12, Folder 254)
  - McLaughlin, Jeanne, 1952-1959 (Box 12, Folder 255)
  - MacLeish, Archibald, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 256)
  - Macrae, Marjorie, 1954, undated (Box 12, Folder 257)
  - McVitty, Kitty
    See: Taquey, Kitty (McVitty), box 22, folders 432-434
  - Mansfield, Barbara, 1946-1954, undated (Box 12, Folder 258)
  - Marquand, Adelaide, 1941-1963, undated (Box 12, Folder 259-260)
  - Mathias, Betty (Murray), 1940-1964 (Box 12, Folder 261)
  - Matthias, Blanche, 1945-1968, undated (Box 12, Folder 262)
  - Millar, Margaret (Bartlett) "Monte", 1930-1938 April (Box 13, Folder 263-278)
  - Millar, Margaret (Bartlett) "Monte", 1938 May-1973, undated (Box 14, Folder 279-288)
  - Millay, Edna St. Vincent, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 289)
  - Miller, Anna, 1947-1960 (Box 14, Folder 290)
  - Milles, Carl, 1943-1948 (Box 14, Folder 291)
    See also: Institutions, committees, and clubs, Series IX. Cranbrook Academy of Art, boxes 194-195, folders 14-15
  - Mitchell, Stephen, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 292)
  - Moreillon, Eglantine, 1960-1973, undated (Box 14, Folder 293-297)
  - Moreillon, Jacques, 1958-1971, undated (Box 15, Folder 298)
  - Morgan, Barbara, 1965-1972 (Box 15, Folder 299)
  - Munroe, Gretel, 1934-1958 (Box 15, Folder 300)
  - Munroe, Ofelia, 1965-1973 (Box 15, Folder 300)
  - Munroe, Sally C., 1955-1957 (Box 15, Folder 300)
  - Munroe, Vernon, Jr., 1928-1929, 1941, 1955-1967, undated (Box 15, Folder 301-302)
  - Murray, Betty
    See: Mathias, Betty (Murray), box 12, folder 261
  - Neild, Dorothy (Hutchison), 1937-1948 (Box 15, Folder 303)
  - Neilson, Elisabeth, 1928-1965, undated (Box 15, Folder 304)
  - Neville, Betsey, 1931-1946, undated (Box 15, Folder 305-306)
  - Neville, Edwin L., 1940-1948 (Box 15, Folder 307)
  - Newton, Eleanor (Forde), 1943-1972, undated (Box 15, Folder 308-312)
  - Newton, James Draper, 1936-1967, undated (Box 15, Folder 313-317)
  - Nicolson, Harold, 1935-1936, 1954-1963, undated (Box 15, Folder 318)
  - Nicolson, Nigel, 1965-1968 (Box 15, Folder 319)
  - Nicolson, Vita (Sackville-West), 1965-1968
    See: Sackville-West, Vita, box 20, folder 393
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 320)
  - Norris, Kathleen, 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 321)
  - Norris, Marta (Brodie), 1944-1968, undated (Box 16, Folder 322)
  - Norton, Lucia
    See: Valentine, Lucia (Norton), box 23, folder 450-458
  - Obermer, Nesta, 1972-1973, undated (Box 16, Folder 323)
  - Oldrin, John, 1949-1971, undated (Box 16, Folder 324-328)
  - Oliff, Ruth (Thomas), 1939-1944 June (Box 16, Folder 329-337)
  - Oliff, Ruth (Thomas), 1944 July-1950, 1951 June-1953 (Box 17, Folder 338-351)
  - Oliff, Ruth (Thomas), 1954-1970, undated (Box 18, Folder 352-364)
  - Orteig, Raymond, 1934-1939 (Box 19, Folder 365)
  - Owen, John, 1956-1972 (Box 19, Folder 365)
  - Painter, Eleanor, 1923-1968, undated (Box 19, Folder 366)
  - Palmer, Paul
  - Parkinson, Betty, 1940-1955, undated (Box 19, Folder 367)
  - Phillips, Rosamond, 1936-1937 (Box 19, Folder 367)
  - Pinchot, Ruth, 1924-1956 (Box 19, Folder 368)
  - Price, Maud, 1945-1961 (Box 19, Folder 369)
  - Privett, Helen K., 1923-1962 (Box 19, Folder 370)
  - Prossor, Anna Fay, 1919-1948, 1973, undated (Box 19, Folder 371)
  - Pryor, Mary Tay, 1956-1973, undated (Box 19, Folder 372)
  - Pryor, Samuel F., 1969-1972 (Box 19, Folder 372)
  - Randolph, Francis, 1963-1973 (Box 19, Folder 373-374)
  - Read, David, 1953-1973, undated (Box 19, Folder 375-376)
  - Regina Laudis Monastery, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 377)
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette, 1935-1970 (Box 19, Folder 378)
  - Rodewald, Elizabeth (Bacon), 1924-1929 (Box 19, Folder 379-381)
  - Rodewald, Elizabeth (Bacon), 1930-1972 (Box 20, Folder 382)
  - Rodman, Selden
  - Rollins, Gordon, 1943-1947, undated (Box 20, Folder 383)
  - Romney, Katrina, 1962-1971, undated (Box 20, Folder 384)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1939-1940 (Box 20, Folder 385)
  - Roots, John, 1939-1940 (Box 20, Folder 386)
  - Rosen, Hazel, 1951-1969 (Box 20, Folder 387)
  - Rosen, John, 1951-1967 (Box 20, Folder 388)
    See also: Institutions, committees, and clubs, Series IX. Institute for Direct Analysis, boxes 197-198, folders 45-47
  - Ross, Nancy Wilson, 1958-1973 (Box 20, Folder 389)
  - Ross, Ruth, 1961-1963, undated (Box 20, Folder 390)
  - Ross, Stanley R., 1955-1958 (Box 20, Folder 391)
  - Rublee, Juliet, 1929-1939, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 392)
  - Sackville-West, Vita, 1936-1955 (Box 20, Folder 393)
  - Saint-Exupéry, Antoine de
    See: Writings, Series VII. Listen! The Wind, boxes 123-127, folders 40-82
  - St. Just, Florrie (Grenfell), 1933-1955, undated (Box 20, Folder 394)
  - Saltonstall, Katharyn, 1959-1968 (Box 20, Folder 395)
  - Saltonstall, William J., 1959-1963 (Box 20, Folder 396)
  - Saunders, Jean, 1959-1973 (Box 20, Folder 397)
  - Savina, Joseph, 1939-1972 (Box 20, Folder 398)
  - Scaravelli, Vanda, 1962-1968 (Box 20, Folder 399)
  - Schabert, Kyrill
    See: Publisher's correspondence, Series III. Pantheon Books, box 73, folders 31-40
  - Scheyer, Ernst, 1944-1970 (Box 20, Folder 400)
  - Schwartz, Lazlo, 1956-1967 (Box 20, Folder 401)
  - Scott-Maxwell, Florida, 1955-1969 (Box 20, Folder 402)
  - Sears, Japsy (Lockett), 1935-1966, undated (Box 20, Folder 403)
  - Sedgwick, Edith L., 1925-1966, undated (Box 20, Folder 404)
  - Shannon, Mary, 1965-1973 (Box 20, Folder 405)
  - Sheldon, Edward, 1945-1959 (Box 20, Folder 406)
  - Shields, Jean
    See: Damon, Jean (Shields), boxes 5-6, folders 98-99
  - Sikorsky, Elizabeth, 1941-1972, undated (Box 21, Folder 407)
  - Sikorsky, Igor, 1943-1948 (Box 21, Folder 408)
  - Skinner, B. F., 1957 (Box 21, Folder 409)
  - Smith, Isadore, 1943-1962, undated (Box 21, Folder 410)
  - Smith, Katherine, 1924-1970, undated (Box 21, Folder 411-413)
  - Smith, Truman, 1943-1957, undated (Box 21, Folder 414-415)
  - Soule, Eleanor (Painter)
    See: Painter, Eleanor, box 19, folder 366
  - Speidel, Hans, 1947-1950 (Box 21, Folder 416)
  - Spender, Stephen, 1950-1964 (Box 21, Folder 417)
  - Stafford, Jean, 1942-1951, undated (Box 21, Folder 418)
  - Stevens, Anna Fay (Prosser)
    See: Prosser, Anna Fay, box 19, folder 371
  - Stevens, George (Box 21)
    See: Publishers correspondence, Series III. Other publishers, boxes 73-74, folders 41-61
  - Stevens, Laura (Brandt), 1927-1955, undated (Box 21, Folder 419-420)
  - Stillman, Elizabeth Goodrich, 1921-1922, undated (Box 21, Folder 421)
  - Stirling, Monica, 1964-1972 (Box 21, Folder 422-424)
  - Stirling, Monica, 1973, undated (Box 22, Folder 425-426)
  - Stodelle, Ernestine
    See: Chamberlain, Ernestine (Stodelle), boxes 4-5, folders 69-85
  - Stuart, Barbara, 1941-1962, undated (Box 22, Folder 427-428)
  - Sturm, Marthe, 1928-1973, undated (Box 22, Folder 429)
  - Sullivan, Katherine, 1935-1971, undated (Box 22, Folder 430)
  - Swanson, Minnie, 1965-1973 (Box 22, Folder 431)
  - Taquey, Kitty (McVitty), 1946-1973, undated (Box 22, Folder 432-434)
  - Thomas, Ruth
    See: Oliff, Ruth (Thomas), boxes 16-18, folders 329-364
  - Thornton, Margaret (Millar)
  - Trask, Elsie (Barber), 1929-1949, 1952-1972, undated (Box 22, Folder 435-437)
  - Trippe, Betty, 1939-1967, undated (Box 22, Folder 437)
  - Trippe, Juan, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 437)
  - Troy, Patricia (Carey), 1942-1972 (Box 22, Folder 438)
  - Utley, Freda, 1942-1955, undated (Box 22, Folder 439-440)
  - Vaillant, George, 1940-1954, undated (Box 22, Folder 441)
  - Vaillant, Sue (Beck)
  - Valentine, Alan, 1934-1939, 1952-1954 (Box 22, Folder 442-443)
  - Valentine, Alan, 1955-1973, undated (Box 23, Folder 444-449)
  - Valentine, Lucia (Norton), 1929-1973, undated (Box 23, Folder 450-458)
  - Van Dusen, Elizabeth, 1935-1973, undated (Box 24, Folder 459)
  - Van Dusen, Henry Pitney, 1940-1969 (Box 24, Folder 460)
  - Waddington, Amy, 1940-1966 (Box 24, Folder 461)
  - Wakefield, Freda, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 462)
  - Walker, Mary Manning
    See: Delafield, Mary (Walker). box 6, folders 107-109
  - Wallace, Dewitt
    See: Publisher's correspondence, Series III. Other publishers, 73-74, folders 41-61
  - Weber, Evelyn, 1939-1968, undated (Box 24, Folder 463)
  - Webster, Jean, 1942-1973, undated (Box 24, Folder 464-467)
  - Weeks, Edward, 1942-1973, undated
    See: Publisher's correspondence, Series III. Atlantic Monthly, box 72, folders 1-6
  - Weiss, Gaspard Etienne, 1958-1967 (Box 24, Folder 468)
  - Wenzel, Magdelene, 1947-1952 (Box 24, Folder 469)
  - Wesley, Katherine, 1937-1957, undated (Box 24, Folder 470)
  - Wheelock, John Hall
  - Whitehead, Alfred North, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 471)
  - Wick, Christine (Gawne), 1940-1950 (Box 24, Folder 471)
  - Wilder, Thornton, 1949-1952 (Box 24, Folder 472)
  - Wilkie, Edith, 1961-1964 (Box 24, Folder 473)
  - Wolff, Helen, 1952-1960 (Box 24, Folder 474)
    See also: Publisher's correspondence, Series III. Harcourt, Brace and World, boxes 72-73, folders 20-26
    See also: Publisher's correspondence, Series III. Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, box 73, folders 27-30
    See also: Publisher's correspondence, Series III. Pantheon Books, box 73, folders 31-40
  - Wolff, Helen, 1961-1972 (Box 24, Folder 475-477)
  - Wolff, Kurt, 1955-1963 (Box 24, Folder 478)
  - Wood, Nancy, 1941-1956 (Box 24, Folder 479)
  - Woolf, Virginia
    See: Nicolson, Harold, box 15, folder 318
  - Yaschmill, Natalie, 1938-1939 (Box 24, Folder 480)
- Family correspondence and personal files, 1906-1974; Series II
  The series is divided into two sections: Family correspondence and Personal files. The former is arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent, with letters of a particular correspondent arranged chronologically. The material in Personal files is organized alphabetically by last name of family member.
  Family correspondence contains letters exchanged by Anne Morrow Lindbergh and members of her immediate family (Charles and her children), members of the Morrow and Lindbergh families, and other relatives. Personal files include correspondence, legal and financial documents, writings, announcements, and newspaper clippings by or about various family members. For Morrow and Cutter family genealogical records, see the Charles A. Lindbergh Papers (MS 325), Series VI, Family correspondence and records.
  - Family correspondence
    - Brown, Marjory W., 1967-1973 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Brown, Reeve (Lindbergh)
      See: Lindbergh, Reeve Morrow, boxes 53-54, folders 436-448
    - Brown, Richard Waldron, 1967-1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Cutter, Annie Elizabeth (Spencer), 1914-1937 (Box 25, Folder 3-6)